Exhibition Records, 1942-2001
Smithsonian Institution Archives
Exhibition Records
1942-2001
Smithsonian Institution Archives, Washington, D.C., osiaref@si.edu
National Museum of American History, Division of Information Technology and Society
SI Records
16 cu. ft. (16 record storage boxes)
Accession 06-276
Descriptive Entry
This accession consists of records which document the planning, development, and installation of "Science in American Life," a major permanent exhibition at the National Museum of American History (NMAH). This exhibition demonstrates how science has changed the way Americans have lived over the past 125 years. Opening on April 27, 1994, "Science in American Life" was 4 years in the making and took the work and collaboration of more than 75 curators, educators, writers, designers and scientific consultants. It occupies 13,000 square feet of exhibition space and includes approximately 600 artifacts, 700 graphics, six video loops, three sound and light displays, six computer interactives, two CD-ROM interactives, 11 mechanical interactives, and a science center featuring 20 hands-on activities.
The exhibition was underwritten by a $5.3 million contribution from the American Chemical Society and was executed under the leadership of Chief Curator, Arthur P. Molella, chair of the Department of the History of Science and Technology. The exhibition begins with an orientation area where people are greeted by 12 host scientists - 10 scientists and two children, represented by life-size photographs and recorded voices - who give a personal, contemporary perspective of the historial materials found in the exhibition. Following this are 6 sections arranged in chronologic order: "Laboratory Science Comes to America, 1876-1920;" "Science for Progress, 1920-1940;" "Mobilizing Science for War, 1940-1960;" "Better Than Nature, 1950-1970;" "Science in the Public Eye, 1970 to the present;" and "Looking Ahead." Developed by Museum Specialist Howard Morrison, "Looking Ahead" focuses on the science of biotechnology and public attitudes about it.
An additional component to the exhibition is the 1,500 square-foot interactive education center known as the "Hands on Science Center." All aspects of the exhibition are documented, including publicity, the anti-science controversy, the glossing over of corporate misdeeds, exhibition design, educational aspects, curriculum development, grant proposals, advisory board meetings, copyrights, audio and video development, feasibility studies, audience surveys, and object acquisition. Subjects and people covered in the exhibition include chemists Ira Remsen and Ellen Henrietta Richards; coal tar and synthetic materials; the Manhattan Project; the first nuclear reactor, Chicago Pile no. 1; the birth control pill; pesticides; DNA; chlorofluorocarbons and atmospheric ozone; the Superconducting Super Collider; genetic engineering; and biotechnology. Materials include correspondence, memoranda, reports, meeting minutes, notes, scripts, contracts, loan agreements, exhibitions proposals, evaluations, budget summaries, design submittals, floor plans, black-and-white photographs and negatives, color photographs and negatives, floppy disks, clippings, and brochures.
Index Terms
This collection is indexed under the following access terms. These are links to collections with related topics, persons or places.
Name
Daniel, Pete; Molella, Arthur P., 1944-; Remsen, Ira, 1846-1927; Allison, David K.; Boyne, Eleanor; Dutta, Smita; Gossel, Pat; Hilke, Deborah D.; Klose, Claudine.; Rossilli, Ann; Schloss, Steve; Tabachnick, Elena; Richards, Ellen H. (Ellen Henrietta), 1842-1911; Manhattan Project (U.S.); National Museum of American History (U.S.); Chicago Pile no. 1; National Museum of American History (U.S.). Dept. of the History of Science and Technology.; American Chemical Society; Science in American Life (Exhibition) (1994: Washington, D.C.)
Subject
Biotechnology; Chlorofluorocarbons; Coal-tar; DNA; Exhibitions; Genetic engineering; Museums -- Educational aspects.; Oral contraceptives; Pesticides; Science -- History; Superconducting Super Collider; Atmospheric ozone; Chemists; Nuclear reactors; Synthetic products
Physical Characteristics of Materials in the Collection
Brochures; Clippings; Manuscripts; Floppy disks; Floor plans; Black-and-white photographs; Color photographs; Black-and-white negatives; Color negatives
- Arthur P. Molella, Chief Curator, Series 1
  - Box 1
    - Science in American Life (SAL) Early Planning, 1983-1990 (3 folders) (Box 1 of 16)
    - SAL correspondence, 1990-1994 (2 folders) (Box 1 of 16)
    - SAL documents and memoranda, 1989-1994 (4 folders) (Box 1 of 16)
    - SAL feasibility study, 1989 (Box 1 of 16)
    - SAL - Jeffery K. Stine, 1989-1990 (Box 1 of 16)
    - SAL - David K. Allison/Jeffery K. Stine files, 1989-1991 (3 folders) (Box 1 of 16)
    - Exhibit Ideas - Offers of Help/Experts, 1989-1990 (Box 1 of 16)
    - American Chemical Society (ACS) Agreement, 1990 (Box 1 of 16)
    - ACS Liaison Committee, 1990-1994 (2 folders) (Box 1 of 16)
    - ACS Advisory Board, 1990-1994 (4 folders) (Box 1 of 16)
    - ACS Meetings, 1991 (Box 1 of 16)
    - SAL (early) book prospectus, 1988 (Box 1 of 16)
    - SAL General Info, 1990 (Box 1 of 16)
    - Background, December 1990 (3 folders) (Box 1 of 16)
    - Sci Prog/December Report, 1990 (Box 1 of 16)
    - December Management Viewgraphs, 1990 (Box 1 of 16)
    - Amendment to Solicitation of Contract, OPPM, March 8, 1992 (Box 1 of 16)
    - SAL Meeting Minutes, 1991 (Box 1 of 16)
    - SAL Publications, 1991-1992 (Box 1 of 16)
    - SAL Related Public Presentations, 1988-1993 (Box 1 of 16)
  - Box 2
    - August Script 1990, with comments from advisor (Box 2 of 16)
    - SAL concept script, 1990 (Box 2 of 16)
    - Script review documents, 1990 (Box 2 of 16)
    - Jeffrey K. Stine's comments, 1991 (Box 2 of 16)
    - Draft narratives and scripts, 1991-1992 (Box 2 of 16)
    - Comments on script, 1992 (Box 2 of 16)
    - SAL outlines, 1991 (Box 2 of 16)
    - SAL designers, 1990-1991 (Box 2 of 16)
    - Materials from William Nevill, 1990-1991 (Box 2 of 16)
    - SAL budget, 1991-1995 (Box 2 of 16)
    - SAL publications program, 1990 (Box 2 of 16)
    - General section ideas, 1991 (Box 2 of 16)
    - Randi Korn - Audience evaluation plan, 1990 (Box 2 of 16)
    - SAL science panels, 1991-1997 (Box 2 of 16)
    - Science panel responses, 1994 (Box 2 of 16)
    - Ask Yourself panels, 1994 (Box 2 of 16)
    - SAL outline - "Science Themes," 1992 (Box 2 of 16)
    - SAL science center, 1992 (Box 2 of 16)
    - Carlene Stephen's notebook, "SAL 21 Dec. 92 - 27 June 93" (Box 2 of 16)
    - Carlene Stephen's notebook, undated (Box 2 of 16)
    - Carlene Stephen's running notes, no. 1 and unlabeled (Box 2 of 16)
    - Carlene Stephen's running notes, no. 2 and no. 3, 1991 (Box 2 of 16)
    - Carlene Stephen's running notes, no. 4 and no. 5, 1991-1992 (Box 2 of 16)
    - Carlene Stephen's running notes, no. 6, 1992 (Box 2 of 16)
    - SAL "Titles," 1992 (Box 2 of 16)
    - SAL "Minority" Themes, 1991-1992 (Box 2 of 16)
    - SAL Smithson Society Proposal, 1993 (Box 2 of 16)
    - SAL NIST, 1990-1992 (Box 2 of 16)
    - Virtual Laboratory, 1990-1991 (Box 2 of 16)
    - Computer interactives, 1991 (Box 2 of 16)
    - Hands on Science Center (HOSC) general materials, 1991 (Box 2 of 16)
    - Learning Center interactives, 1990-1991 (Box 2 of 16)
    - Oxychem proposal, 1990 (Box 2 of 16)
    - Oxychem project, 1991 (Box 2 of 16)
    - Oxychem/Tom Snyder Productions, 1994 (Box 2 of 16)
    - SAL script - "Scientific Progress,' 1992 (Box 2 of 16)
    - Exhibition - General, schedule, etc.; 1992-1994 (Box 2 of 16)
    - SAL Women in Science/Power House Museum, 1993-1994 (Box 2 of 16)
    - SAL Nova, etc., 1993-1994 (Box 2 of 16)
    - SAL "Electronic Field Trip," 1994 (Box 2 of 16)
    - SAL - SEF Grant Proposal, 1994 (Box 2 of 16)
    - SAL SetQuest, 1995 (Box 2 of 16)
    - SAL poster (Box 2 of 16)
    - SAL brochure, 1993-1994 (Box 2 of 16)
    - Main labels, comments, 1992-1993 (2 folders) (Box 2 of 16)
  - Box 3
    - Comments - Advisory, 1990-1992 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Sound and light, 1993 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Videos, 1992-1994 (2 folders) (Box 3 of 16)
    - College films, 1992 (Box 3 of 16)
    - SAL curriculum project, 1993 (Box 3 of 16)
    - SAL catalog, 1993-1994 (Box 3 of 16)
    - SAL catalog bibliography, 1994 (Box 3 of 16)
    - SAL CD-ROM, 1994-1995 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Hands on Science Center, 1993 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Object list, 1993 (Box 3 of 16)
    - SAL punch lists, 1994 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Estimate of NMAH staff time devoted to SAL (Box 3 of 16)
    - Memoranda regarding collection management, 1993-1994 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Notes, plans, 1991-1992 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 1 - Content development - Orientation, 1993-1994 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 1 - Introduction/orientation, 1992-1994 (2 folders) (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 1 - Mizuki and Lawrence interview transcripts (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 1 - Host scientist interviews transcripts, 1993 (2 folders) (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 1 - Orientation interview transcripts, 1993 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 2 - Content development, 1992-1994 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 2 - General, 1991-1993 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 2 - Remsen's Lab, 1991-1995 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 2 - Remsen Lab mannequins, 1993 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 2 - Kristin pure food, 1993 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 3 - Content development, 1991-1994 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 3 - General, 1991-1993 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 3 - Kodachrome, 1991 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 3 - DuPont and world's fairs, 1992-1994 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 3 - World War II, 1991 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 3 - Manhattan Project artifact, 1990-1991 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 3 - Jeff Sturchio's comments, 1993 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 3 - Memorandum from Lou Drummeter, 1993 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 3 - Letter from Hot Cell Services, 1994 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 4 - Content development, 1993-1994 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 4 - General, 1990-1998 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 4 - Nuclear medicine, 1993 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 4 - Nuclear bomb, weapons testing, radiation; 1991-1994 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 5 - Content development, 1991-1993 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 5 - General, 1991-1993 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 5 - Plastics, 1991-1992 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 5 - Home, 1992-1993 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 5 - Pesticides, 1992 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 5 - Garbage, 1993 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 5 - The pill and sexual revolution, 1992-1994 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 5 - Birth control letters (Patricia Gossel), 1994-1998 (2 folders) (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 5 - Visitor's perspectives, 1991-1993 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 5 - Audience research reports, 1992-1993 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 5 - Comments regarding "Pesticides then and now" and "Bob's weekend," 1993-1994 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 6 - Content development, 1991-1994 (Box 3 of 16)
    - Section 6 - General, 1992-1993 (Box 3 of 16)
  - Box 4
    - Looking Ahead, 1992-1993 (2 folders) (Box 4 of 16)
    - Content development - Miscellaneous, 1992-1994 (Box 4 of 16)
    - SAL script, 1993-1996 (4 folders) (Box 4 of 16)
    - Public relations, 1990-1991 (Box 4 of 16)
    - SAL Publicity Pre-Opening, 1994 (Box 4 of 16)
    - SAL Press Briefing, April 26, 1994 (Box 4 of 16)
    - Publicity brochure, 1993-1994 (Box 4 of 16)
    - SAL Near Opening Preparation (exhibition, videos, etc.), 1993-1994 (2 folders) (Box 4 of 16)
    - SAL Opening Events, 1994 (Box 4 of 16)
    - SAL symposia, seminars, etc.; 1994 (Box 4 of 16)
    - SAL Publicity - Markup of SAL Script by SI Public Relations, 1994 (Box 4 of 16)
    - Publicity, 1993-1996 (8 folders) (Box 4 of 16)
    - SAL Publicity - "Technology Review," 1994 (Box 4 of 16)
    - SAL Opening Post-Opening Events, 1994 (Box 4 of 16)
    - SAL Symposium, Seminars, etc.; 1994 (Box 4 of 16)
    - SAL Publicity Post-Opening Revisions/Controversy, 1995-1996 (Box 4 of 16)
    - SAL Post-Opening Revisions/Controversy, 1995-1996 (2 folders) (Box 4 of 16)
    - SAL Post-Opening Revisions Debate, 1995-1996 (2 folders) (Box 4 of 16)
    - SAL Controversy and related historical controversy, 1994-1997 (Box 4 of 16)
    - SAL Controversy (APS Revisions) (Box 4 of 16)
  - Box 5
    - SAL Controversy, 1994-1996 (7 folders) (Box 5 of 16)
    - SAL Tracking Study (Exit Survey) Zahava Doering, 1995 (Box 5 of 16)
    - SAL Doering Report, 1995 (2 folders) (Box 5 of 16)
    - SAL Changes, 1995-1996 (Box 5 of 16)
    - SAL E-mail and letters to the Editor, 1994-1995 (Box 5 of 16)
    - SAL Post-Opening Talks, Tours, etc.; 1994 (Box 5 of 16)
    - SAL Post Mortem, 1994-1995 (Box 5 of 16)
    - SAL Post-Opening Evaluation, 1995 (Box 5 of 16)
    - Commerce Science and Technology Fellowship Program tour, 1997 (Box 5 of 16)
- Claudine Klose, Project Manager, Series 2
  - Box 5
    - PR Brochure, 1993 (Box 5 of 16)
    - PR/Opening events, 1993-1994 (Box 5 of 16)
    - Publications, 1990-1993 (Box 5 of 16)
    - NIST, 1990-1992 (Box 5 of 16)
    - EPA - Garbage, 1993 (Box 5 of 16)
    - EPA - Bob's weekend, 1993 (Box 5 of 16)
    - Hardware requests, 1993 (Box 5 of 16)
    - Pioneer video equipment, 1991-1993 (Box 5 of 16)
    - Old Proposals "Dead," 1991-1993 (Box 5 of 16)
    - Garbage fundraising, unsuccessful, 1991-1993 (Box 5 of 16)
    - In-Kind Requests HOSC - Pending, unsuccessful, 1993 (Box 5 of 16)
    - Electronic Field Trip, 1994 (Box 5 of 16)
    - Exhibit meetings, 1990-1991 (Box 5 of 16)
    - SAL space, 1991-1992 (Box 5 of 16)
    - Space problem, 1993 (Box 5 of 16)
    - SAL Team organization, 1989-1993 (Box 5 of 16)
    - SAL Maintenance (Box 5 of 16)
    - Fundraising, 1991-1994 (Box 5 of 16)
    - Acknowledgement plaques (Box 5 of 16)
    - SEF proposal, 1991-1993 (Box 5 of 16)
    - SEF grant, 1994 (Box 5 of 16)
    - DCAT Foundation, 1993-1994 (Box 5 of 16)
    - Virtual Reality Proposal, 1991-1992 (Box 5 of 16)
    - Tom Synder, 1993-1994 (Box 5 of 16)
    - Oxychem, 1991 (Box 5 of 16)
    - Oxychem RFP, 1992-1993 (Box 5 of 16)
    - Looking Ahead, 1991-1994 (Box 5 of 16)
  - Box 6
    - SAL design RFP, 1990-1991 (Box 6 of 16)
    - SAL design RFP back-up, 1991 (Box 6 of 16)
    - Staples Charles, 1991-1992 (Box 6 of 16)
    - Staples Charles response to RFP, Volume II, Technical Proposal, 1991 (Box 6 of 16)
    - Diversity issues, 1990-1992 (Box 6 of 16)
    - HOSC, 1992-1994 (3 folders) (Box 6 of 16)
    - Production meetings, 1993-1994 (Box 6 of 16)
    - Installation, 1994 (Box 6 of 16)
    - Design, 1993-1994 (Box 6 of 16)
    - Mannequins (Box 6 of 16)
    - Looking Ahead - Contract, 1993-1994 (3 folders) (Box 6 of 16)
    - Science Advisor, 1991 (Box 6 of 16)
    - Product development, 1991 (Box 6 of 16)
    - Museum shops, 1993-1994 (Box 6 of 16)
    - Correspondence - Ned Heindel (ACS President), 1991-1993 (Box 6 of 16)
    - Correspondence - Bill Neville, 1991-1992 (Box 6 of 16)
    - Correspondence - Ann Messmore, 1990-1994 (Box 6 of 16)
    - Correspondence - Meeting, November 1991 (Box 6 of 16)
    - Correspondence - Meeting, May 1992 (Box 6 of 16)
    - ACS/SI Advisory Board (Notes) (Box 6 of 16)
    - ACS - General, 1990 (Box 6 of 16)
    - Chedd-Angier, 1993-1994 (Box 6 of 16)
    - Interconnections/Garbage, 1991-1993 (Box 6 of 16)
  - Box 7
    - Garbage Dilemma - Audubon, 1992-1993 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Maintenance, 1993-1995 (Accession 12-377) (Box 7 of 16)
    - Outside Help - Interactives, 1992 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Mechanical Interactives contract, 1993 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Interactive fabrication, 1992 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Life of interactives (Accession 12-377) (Box 7 of 16)
    - Women in Science proposals, 1993-1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Computer graphics/programming, 1992-1993 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Education planning, 1988-1993 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Docent training, 1994 (Accession 12-377) (Box 7 of 16)
    - Self-guide, 1994-1997 (Accession 12-377) (Box 7 of 16)
    - HOSC planning, 1990-1991 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Chronology Interactives, 1992-1993 (Box 7 of 16)
    - CD-ROMs, 1993-1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Sound Light, 1992-1993 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Intro Hosts/Timeline, 1993 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Contracts Pending, 1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Contract - Adame Custom Creations, 1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Contract - American University, 1992-1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Contract - Aris (construction), 1993-1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Contract - Chedd-Angier, 1993-1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Contract - Douglas/Gallagher, 1993-1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Contract - Eric Colbert, 1993-1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Contract - Commercial Glass, 1993-1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Contract - Fisher Hamilton, 1993-1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Contract - Elizabeth Ivie, 1993 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Contract - Robert Kargon, 1990-1993 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Contract - Labyrinth Electrical, 1993-1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Contract - McLean Media, 1993-1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Contract - New Media Group, 1993-1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Contract - Newson Model Making, 1993-1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Contract - Colin Stevens, 1993 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Contract - Helen Weiss Productions, 1993-1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Department of Energy (DOE) grant, 1993-1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Fund number - 8455B400, 1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Fund number - 845590-01, 1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Fund number - 845590-02, 1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Fund number - 1255X401, 1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - No Cost to SAL, 1993-1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Registration of SAL objects, 1993 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Copyright Issues, 1993-1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Office expenses, 1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Photographic expenses, 1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - General and computer expenses, 1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Audio-visual expenses, 1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Production expenses, 1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Conservation and registrar expenses, 1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Advisory Board expenses, 1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Looking Ahead expenses, 1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - HOSC expenses, 1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Chronology expenses, 1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Publicity and publications expenses, 1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Milestone reviews, 1990-1993 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Discrepancy Back-Up, 1992-1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Final Report Back-Up, 1992-1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - West End planning, 1982-1983 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Electricity Corner, 1983 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Overview - The Research Revolution: Science in American Life, 1988 (Box 7 of 16)
    - The Research Revolution (Box 7 of 16)
    - How is Research Done, 1988 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Who are the Scientists, 1988 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Research Region: Silicon Valley, 1988-1989 (Box 7 of 16)
    - The Beltway Society: Transformations of the American Landscape, 1989 (Box 7 of 16)
    - The Processed Image, 1988 (Box 7 of 16)
    - The Culture of Science (Box 7 of 16)
    - The Risk-Managed Society, 1989 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Counterpoint: Science in Japanese Life (Box 7 of 16)
    - Conclusion: Research and Our Conception of Ourselves (Box 7 of 16)
    - "Life of Science," 1989 (Box 7 of 16)
    - "Science in Everyday Life," 1989 (Box 7 of 16)
    - James Smithson Society Proposal, 1993 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Special Exhibition Fund (SEF) Proposal, 1994 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Advisory Board - HOSC, 1993 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Advisory Board - Chron/Intro, 1993 (Box 7 of 16)
    - Advisory Board - Looking Ahead, 1993 (Box 7 of 16)
  - Box 8
    - Advisory Board - Meeting minutes, 1990-1993 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Advisory Board - Biographies (Box 8 of 16)
    - Advisory Board - General, 1990-1991 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Advisory Board - Liaison Committee, 1993 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Advisory Board - Newsletter, 1991-1993 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Advisory Board - Comments from November 11, 1993 meeting (Box 8 of 16)
    - Advisory Board - Mailing, August 1991 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Advisory Board - Mailing, October 1991 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Advisory Board - Mailing, June 1991 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Advisory Board - Mailing and meeting, May 17, 1992 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Advisory Board - Mailing, October 1992 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Advisory Board - Mailing, November 1993 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Management review - December 1990 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Management review - June 1, 1991 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Management review - February 10, 1992 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Management review - November 8, 1992 (Box 8 of 16)
    - SAL press clippings, 1991-1993 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Publicity, 1991 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Chronological files - January 1994 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Chronological files - December 1993 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Chronological files - November 1993 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Chronological files - October 1993 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Chronological files - September 1993 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Chronological files - August 1993 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Chronological files - July 1993 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Chronological files - June 1993 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Chronological files - May 1993 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Chronological files - April 1993 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Chronological files - March 1993 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Chronological files - February 1993 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Chronological files - January 1993 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Chronological files - December 1992 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Chronological files - November 1992 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Chronological files - October1992 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Chronological files - September 1992 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Chronological files - August 1992 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Chronological files - July 1992 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Chronological files - June 1992 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Chronological files - May 1992 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Chronological files - April 1992 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Chronological files - March 1992 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Chronological files - February 1992 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Chronological files - January 1992 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Chronological files - December 1991 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Chronological files - November 1991 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Chronological files - October 1991 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Chronological files - September 1991 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Chronological files - August 1991 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Chronological files - July 1991 (Box 8 of 16)
    - Chronological files - June 1991 (Box 8 of 16)
  - Box 9
    - Chronological files - May 1991 (Box 9 of 16)
    - Chronological files - April 1991 (Box 9 of 16)
    - Chronological files - March 1991 (Box 9 of 16)
    - Chronological files - February 1991 (Box 9 of 16)
    - Chronological files - January 1991 (Box 9 of 16)
    - Chronological files - December 1990 (Box 9 of 16)
    - Chronological files - November 1990 (Box 9 of 16)
    - Chronological files - October 1990 (Box 9 of 16)
    - Chronological files - September 1990 (Box 9 of 16)
    - Chronological files - August 1990 (Box 9 of 16)
    - Chronological files - May 1990 (Box 9 of 16)
    - D. D. Hilke, 1989 (Box 9 of 16)
    - American Chemical Society (ACS) meeting - May 5-6, 1988 (Box 9 of 16)
    - Oxychem, 1990-1993 (Box 9 of 16)
    - ACS Library loans, 1990-1991 (Box 9 of 16)
    - Staples and Charles, Ltd., 1991 (Box 9 of 16)
    - Staples and Charles package, 1991 (Box 9 of 16)
    - Staples and Charles sketches, 1992 (Box 9 of 16)
    - Staples and Charles notes, 1991-1992 (Box 9 of 16)
    - Staples and Charles correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 9 of 16)
    - Staples and Charles plans, 1991-1992 (Box 9 of 16)
    - Ned Heindel, 1990-1992 (2 folders) (Box 9 of 16)
    - Video research and production, 1991-1993 (2 folders) (Box 9 of 16)
    - Advisory Board, 1989-1993 (2 folders) (Box 9 of 16)
    - Liaison Committee, 1990-1994 (2 folders) (Box 9 of 16)
    - SAL schedule, 1990-1993 (2 folders) (Box 9 of 16)
    - Design floor plans (Box 9 of 16)
    - Concept script, 1990 (Box 9 of 16)
    - Main labels, 1993 (Box 9 of 16)
    - Advisory Committee progress report - Alicia M. Cutler, 1991 (Box 9 of 16)